Sea Evil
Ghost Ship is a horror, mystery, thriller film directed by Steve Beck.
After discovering a passenger ship missing since 1962 floating adrift on
the Bering Sea, salvagers claim the vessel as their own.
Once they begin towing the ghost ship towards harbor, a series of bizarre occurrences happen and the group
becomes trapped inside the ship, which they soon learn is inhabited by a demonic creature.
Captain Sean Murphy, played by Gabriel Byrne.
Maureen Epps, played by Julianna Margulies.
Jack Ferriman, played by Desmond Harrington.
Dodge, played by Ron Eldard.
Greer, played by Isaiah Washington.
Munder, played by Karl Urban.
Ghost Ship is a 2002 supernatural horror film directed by Steve
Beck from a screenplay by Mark Hanlon and John Pogue.
Its plot follows a marine salvage crew in the Bering Sea who discover a mysterious ocean liner that disappeared in 1962 and stars an ensemble
cast of Gabriel Byrne, Julianna Margulies, Ron Eldard, Desmond Harrington, Isaiah Washington, Alex Dimitriades, and Karl Urban.
Shot in Australia and Canada, It was released
theatrically in North America on October 25, 2002.
It received generally negative reviews but was a commercial success,
grossing $68.3 million worldwide on a $20 million budget.
The film explores themes of treasure, cruise, halloween, pilot, ghost ship.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.